Man of God, please, help me.
My bone got broken since six months ago, due to an accident.
I am using crutches to walk.
Please, help me, man of God.
How do you know that Jesus would heal you?
I know that God would help me because He is still keeping me alive until now.
What would happen if you are not healed?
I believe that He will heal me.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you are not healed, what would happen?
He would heal me. He is my God. He is supposed to heal me.
He would heal me.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I have been waiting for this time. He would heal me.
But answer this simple question: If you are not healed, what would be the state of your mind?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Man of God, I would be healed. I know I would be healed.
This is the last bus stop that I have.
I have gone to many places.
I have been talking to people in Liberia that I would come here and they would see me get healed.
You say this is the last bus stop?
This is a last bus stop.
So if this bus stop is not for you we would create another bust stop.
It is the last bus stop.
I can't go to a different place. This is the last bus stop.
I am supposed to be healed by the grace of God.
I am asking this question because it is easy to lose your miracle when you have not been grounded in the Word.
You can only maintain that miracle when you are grounded.
When you are grounded, submit to the Word after healing.
If you have been grounded and you receive the miracle,
automatically, you will be able to maintain it.
If you have not been grounded in the Word, you can receive the miracle as well
but you have to automatically submit to the Word so that you will be able to maintain it.
My father here has not been grounded in the Word.
So, if God heals him, he has to automatically submit to the Word of God for maintenance.
Are you listening to me, sir?
Yes, sir.
The fact that you watch Emmanuel TV every day and you sleep with Emmanuel TV,
do you actually do what Emmanuel TV is saying, what you listen to?
Are you doing what the Word says?
That is the question.
What he is talking now is by feeling, emotion.
He is saying what he has been seeing happening to others.
It is not that he has received a conviction, message or revelation to come here.
For him, it's about, "I have seen people get healed, so, I am going there".
Let's hear from our mother.
How are you mum?
We are seeing you sitting here.
What revelation have you received that actually let to your coming here?
Man of God, I need help, healing.
I know you need healing.
It is revelation that brings healing.
Yes, man of God.
Meditation brings revelation.
The product of revelation is healing, deliverance and all that.
What revelation have you received?
Have you received any revelation from God concerning your health, your coming here?
If not, after your healing, you have to submit.
Yes, man of God.
Submit to the authority of the Word of God - that is the only way you can maintain your miracle.
People complain that their miracle is lost.
Why won't your miracle be lost when the Word is not the standard for your life?
The Word must be the standard for your life.
If the Word has not been the standard for your life, you can also receive healing
but immediately you receive from Him, let the Word be the standard for your life to maintain it.
That is the only way you can maintain it.
The one who gave you should be the one to maintain you.
If Jesus gives, Jesus should be the One to maintain.
How are you?
Fine, man of God.
We are seeing you here today; you are welcome.
Thank you, man of God.
What message do you have concerning your coming here?
The message I have is that God is here, from what I have been seeing on Emmanuel TV.
How do you know that God is here?
How do you know God is inviting you?
Have you received God's invitation ?
My spirit tells me that God invited me here, and He made it possible for me to be here.
You spirit tells you?
Yes, man of God.
Where is the invitation?
Where is the invitation given to you to come?
It is spiritual.
It is my conviction.
Thank you, you are welcome.
Well, in some occasions too, if you are not invited and you go there, you may be received.
You would be received. It is not only invited people that enter the hall or are being attended to.
You may not be having an invitation but you go to the occasion and be received.
So, if you do not have God's invitation to come here and you come,
after He has attended to you, you have to submit to God.
If not, it is all a waste.
There is no way you can maintain what you have received from God without God.
Tell your neighbour.
In the world, you can receive something from A and run to B to maintain it.
In the case of Jesus, once you receive something from Him,
He should be the One to maintain it for you.
If not, you will loose it.
This is why we run helter-skelter today.
You were there yesterday but where are you today?
You think you can rob Him.
It's all for the salvation of your soul.
Be ready to stay with Him for maintenance.
You lack maintenance;
stay with Him for maintenance.
Tell your neighbour.
Stay with Him for maintenance.
Again.
Because the blessing of Jesus attracts attack.
The healing of Jesus attracts attack.
The breakthrough from Jesus attracts attack.
When you receive the healing now, attack would be looking for you.
The healing is like honey.
Once you are given that honey, insects seek it and find it.
You will see insects looking for it without invitation.
So, He must be the One to maintain that honey for you.
You cannot maintain it; only Him can maintain it.
Let God's Word be the standard for your life.
Thank you.
TT Mel Flowers
RV Robert Begier 13/06/2018